Sync by Thanh Hoang www.Itfriend.ORG www.MY-SUBS.com
I made it!
A year and a half ago,
You're Rocking the Boat."
Now here we are, at the top
Nationals!
I want to hit up Central
Park, get my frolic on.
I want to throw stuff off the Brooklyn Bridge.
You guys, hold on. I mean,
Okay, Mr. Bossy Pants.
But I think we might have some time for a tune before we leave.
♪ Start spreading the news ♪
♪ I'm leaving today ♪
♪ I want to be a part of it ♪
♪ New York, New York... ♪.
Guys, I have news.
To celebrate our impending win at Nationals,
I got us all 13 tickets to Broadway's longest-running
Cats!
Yeah, you did.
You might want to check the dates on those tickets, Rachel,
He did seem crazy.
Charged my credit card
Okay, welcome
Your rooms are on the seventh floor.
Great.
You planning on fitting all those kids in two rooms?
Yeah, well, it's all we can afford.
I was just thinking
You guys in for the show choir competition? Yeah. Why?
Most of the other teams split by sexual orientation.
Oh. Did you know that
New York City was built
I'm pretty sure that's not true.
Oh, I'm just pretty.
Hi.
I'm surprised at how well
Quinn is taking the breakup.
I guess I was wrong about her being a vindictive harpy.
I guess she just accepted the inevitable.
Or maybe she's just distracted
New York. I know I am.
Hey, do you know why it smells like it's wet here all the time?
No. So, what's going on with you and Jessie?
I don't know. He keeps texting me.
But I told him I don't want to talk till I get back.
No boys, no distractions until we win that trophy.
Hey, Finn, where the hell is Puckerman?
Um...
I'll have a Manhattan.
Do you even know what's in a Manhattan?
Yeah, me, for the first time.
Which is why I want to celebrate with a cocktail.
Guys, group meeting, in the room now.
Do you know that I can get ahi tartare and a steak
I feel like Eloise.
I have pills for that.
All right, guys, this is your time.
Now, you are all on lockdown
I want at least two solid verses by the time I get back.
Aren't you going to help us?
Uh, um... I will be back
I have to head to the theater to, uh, fill out some paperwork.
Broadway.
♪ In the middle of the night
I'm in bed alone ♪
♪ Don't care if you're glass, paper or Styrofoam ♪
♪ When I need some water, baby ♪
♪ Coffee or gin ♪
♪ You're the only thing ♪
♪ I want to put them in ♪
♪ My cup, my cup, sayin' what's up? ♪
♪ To my cup, my cup ♪
♪ More of a friend than a silly pup, my cup ♪
♪ You know what it is ♪
♪ Saying what's up? ♪
♪ To my cup ♪
♪ I'm saying what's up?
To my cup ♪
♪ I'm saying what's up? ♪
♪ To my cup. ♪.
Awesome.
Hold on.
Are you singing about a cup?
Yeah, totally.
We got to get out of here.
Wait. No, no, no. Mr. Shue gave us explicit instructions...
To write a song, and our problem is,
Quinn's right. We're in the artists capital of the world.
Poets, musicians, actors, playwrights.
Every dreamer that's ever lived has passed through this city.
And if we want our dreams to come true, we need to be
Guys, I don't think this is a good idea.
I mean, we still got those songs to write.
If we don't write them, we're going to lose.
No. They're right.
Can't you hear the city calling to you?
We don't need to write songs for Nationals.
New York's going to write them for us.
♪ I don't like cities, but I like New York ♪
♪ The famous places to visit are so many ♪
♪ Other places make me feel like a dork ♪
♪ I told my grandpa
I wouldn't miss on any ♪
♪ Los Angeles is for people who sleep ♪
♪ Got to see the whole town ♪
♪ Right from Yonkers on down to the Bay ♪
♪ Paris and London, oh, baby, you can keep ♪
♪ Baby, you can keep ♪
♪ Other cities always make me mad ♪
♪ Other places always make me sad ♪
♪ No other city ever made me glad ♪
♪ Except New York, New York ♪
♪ It's a wonderful town ♪
♪ I love New York ♪
♪ New York ♪
♪ If you don't like my attitude ♪
♪ Then you can get lost ♪
♪ Manhattan women are dressed in silk and satin ♪
♪ Just go to Texas, isn't that where they golf? ♪
♪ There's just one thing that's important in Manhattan ♪
♪ New York is not for little wussies ♪
♪ Who scream ♪
♪ Pick up a date, maybe 7:00 or 8:00 ♪
♪ Paris and London, oh, baby, you can keep ♪
♪ Baby, you can keep ♪
♪ Other cities always make me mad ♪
♪ Make me mad ♪
♪ Other places always make me sad ♪
♪ Make me sad ♪
♪ No other city ever made me glad ♪
♪ Except New York, New York ♪
♪ It's a wonderful town ♪
♪ I love New York ♪
♪ New York ♪
♪ We sailed the seas and we've been the world over ♪
♪ Made the Mandalay ♪
♪ We've seen the sphinx and we've seen the Cliffs of Dover ♪
♪ And we can safely say ♪
♪ New York ♪
♪ Other cities always make me mad ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh, oh ♪
♪ Other places always make me sad ♪
♪ New York ♪
♪ No other city ever made me glad ♪
♪ Except New York, New York ♪
♪ It's a wonderful town ♪
♪ I love New York ♪
♪ New York, yeah ♪
♪ New York, New York ♪
♪ I love New York ♪
♪ New York, yeah ♪
♪ New York, New York. ♪.
Hey, can I try something out on you guys?
I think that one of our songs
I just want to win.
We all know that
Awesome.
Okay, can we just talk about the Jewish elephant in the room?
Ask her out, dude.
Who? Rachel? But she's totally into Jessie right now.
You're in New York, the city of love.
I thought that was Paris.
Anything's possible here.
You need to ask her out tonight.
Take her
This is your shot, dude.
If I was in love with a girl,
I'd totally go for it.
♪ If you're not home,
I'll sit here on your doorstep ♪
♪ Button up my coat and wait ♪
♪ We'll go upstairs ♪
♪ Close the curtains and we're all set ♪
♪ To pick up where we left again ♪
♪ There's question marks hanging over us ♪
♪ But we won't give the time of day, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ 'Cause all we got is these few stolen seconds ♪
♪ And we can't let them go to waste ♪
♪ The stars collide ♪
♪ We come back to life, we come back to life ♪
♪ The sparks, they fly ♪
♪ One look in your eyes ♪
♪ My heart's open wide ♪
♪ I know time's running out now ♪
♪ But we'll hold back the sun somehow ♪
♪ See the sky ♪
♪ We've still got tonight ♪
♪ We've still got tonight. ♪
April?
She's still at dinner with the rest of the crew.
Oh. Sorry I was just trying out a new idea for the show.
I've been working here 25 years.
Seen a lot of talent come and go.
And let me tell you something, kid.
You got it.
Hi.
What's so important?
Uh, these are for you.
I thought since, uh, we're both captains and all,
The tie and... flowers,
Central Park?
Oh, it's a... a work date.
Uh, totally professional.
Oh, my God, I can't believe we're at Sardi's.
Sardi's! The birthplace of the Tony Award.
What's a salad "nicose"?
One day they're gonna
I like the way you dream so big.
I don't know how to do that.
You look so pretty tonight.
Rachel, I... I have something to say to you.
Oh, my God!
That's Patti LuPone!
Oh, no, oh, my God, I can't do this.
No. No, I have to... I mean, if not for me, then for Kurt.
I mean, he'd kill me if I didn't. Okay.
Excuse me, uh, Miss LuPone?
I have to say that you're my idol.
Well, thank you.
That's very sweet of you.
Are you an actress?
Yes. I'm-I'm in high school.
We're in town for the National
Show Choir Championship.
I was in choir in high school.
It was my favorite class.
What's your name?
Rachel Berry.
Well, Rachel Berry, promise me one thing...
You'll never give up.
Yes, Ms. LuPone, I promise.
Good luck.
Thank you.
He's cute.
Being in New York is like...
Falling in love over and over again every minute.
Tonight felt like one of those awesome nights
All we need now is just a group of street singers
♪ Oh, this is the night ♪
♪ It's a beautiful night ♪
♪ And we call it ♪
♪ Bella notte ♪
♪ Look at the skies ♪
♪ They have stars in their eyes ♪ Wait.
♪ On this lovely ♪ This is the moment.
♪ Bella notte... ♪ in those romantic comedies where... I kiss you.
I thought this was just a work date.
Really?
♪ ♪
♪ You'll find enchantment ♪ No.
♪ Here ♪
♪ The night will weave its magic spell ♪
♪ When the one you love is near ♪
I can't.
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ This is the night ♪
♪ And the heavens ♪ Take a chance on me.
♪ Are right ♪
♪ On this lovely ♪
♪ Bella ♪ I'm sorry, Finn.
♪ Notte ♪ I can't.
♪ ♪
♪ This is the night ♪
♪ And the heavens ♪
♪ Are right ♪
♪ On this lovely ♪
♪ Bella ♪
♪ Notte... ♪
Rachel, wake up, wake up.
Why? We're going to breakfast at Tiffany's.
We're gonna get into so much trouble for this.
How awesome are these bagels?!
Mm. It's the water.
Ah, you're the only one besides me
Which is why I have a secret to tell you.
When we graduate I'm coming back here and I'm going to college here.
This is where I belong.
I am so coming, too.
Really?
And I talked to Blaine; he's on board as well. Good.
What am I gonna do about Finn?
I mean, I... I think he wants to get back together,
I can't have anything keep me
Bring him along.
He'll be great if we need to move anything heavy. No.
Finn won't come... he's too much of a country boy.
Ah, the age-old dilemma:
Love or career?
You're gonna have to make a choice.
I don't... I don't know how.
I do.
Follow me.
W-W-Wait!
Wait.
♪ ♪
I love this show, but it's not helping me make up my mind.
We have to go in.
Strike that.
We have to break in.
No, we-we can't be in here.
They say that if you
It's 9:00 a. M....
Hey!
You're not supposed to be in here.
We're extras.
Th-they told us to come early.
We're, um, being...
Being fitted for our munchkin costumes.
You're from Indiana, right?
Ohio, actually.
And you got some big Broadway dream
Look, we're-we're really sorry...
You got 15 minutes.
♪ ♪
If you have to make a choice,
How?
Sing.
Picture yourself standing in front of a full audience,
There's no orchestra.
Make one.
In your mind.
♪ I'm limited ♪
♪ Just look at me ♪
♪ And just look at you ♪
♪ You can do all I couldn't do ♪
♪ Glinda ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Now it's up ♪
♪ To you... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've heard it said ♪
♪ That people come into our lives ♪
♪ For a reason ♪
♪ Bringing something we must learn ♪
♪ Well, I don't ♪
♪ Know if I believe ♪
♪ That's true ♪
♪ But I know I'm who I am today ♪
♪ Because I knew you ♪
♪ Like a ship blown from its mooring ♪
♪ By a wind off the sea ♪
♪ Like a seed dropped by a skybird ♪
♪ In a distant wood ♪
♪ Who can say ♪
♪ If I've been changed ♪
♪ For the better? ♪
♪ But because I knew you ♪
♪ Because I knew you ♪
♪ I have been changed ♪
♪ For good ♪
♪ And just to clear the air ♪
♪ I ask forgiveness ♪
♪ For the things I've done you blame me for ♪
♪ But then I guess we know ♪
♪ There's blame to share ♪
♪ And none of it seems to matter ♪
♪ Anymore... ♪
♪ Like a comet ♪
♪ Pulled from orbit ♪
♪ Like a ship blown ♪
♪ As it passes the sun ♪
♪ From its moorings by a wind off the sea ♪
♪ Like a stream that meets a boulder ♪
♪ Like a seed dropped ♪
♪ Halfway through the wood ♪
♪ By a bird in the wood ♪
♪ Who can say... ♪
♪ If I've been changed ♪
♪ For the better ♪
♪ Because I knew you ♪
♪ I have been changed... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ For good... ♪.
Thank you, Kurt.
I see it now.
I don't have to choose between...
My career and... love,
I mean... this stage,
Broadway, New York...
...that's my true love.
Quinn! Quit hogging the bathroom.
I needs to re-pencil my eyebrows on.
Doesn't she get...
It's all yours.
Everybody's already in the other room working. Oh, yeah?
Is Mr. Shue in there?
'Cause I think I'm gonna tell him
You can't do that... he'll have to suspend them.
And then there goes
You know what?
We get it.
You're pissed about Finn dumping your sweet ass.
Get over it.
I don't want to get over it! Okay?
The only person that you're sabotaging here is yourself.
I don't care about some stupid show choir competition!
Well, you should!
Because this is
Aren't we supposed to be the popular girls?
So why can't we have our dreams come true?
She has love, Tina has it,
I just want somebody to love me.
I think I know how to make you feel better.
I'm flattered, Santana, but
I'm really not that into that.
No.
No, I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about a haircut.
Yes, totally.
I'm sorry about the pillows.
I mean, this really was a... a wake-up call for me
Look, I get it.
Kids are kids.
Good luck at Nationals.
Thank you.
I'll second that.
And why would you be wishing my glee club luck at Nationals?
Oh, I wasn't talking about the glee club.
I was wishing you luck in your Broadway debut.
How did you find out?
It's all over the Broadway blogosphere.
And by Broadway blogosphere,
I mean the one blog that actually cares about Broadway.
Can I give you a piece of advice?
Don't tell your kids.
It'll just shake their confidence at Nationals
I hate my kids.
I would literally whip them if I could.
Every time I see them achieving...
Just reminds me of everything
I missed out on.
I love my kids.
What? No, you don't.
They're hideous.
My kids are at least attractive.
Yours look like they haven't been baked properly.
I've watched them grow into mature young men and women.
And that's been the joy of my life.
You're tearing up.
People are starting to stare.
I bet they think I just broke up with you.
See you on the ice, Schuester.
All right, guys, who's up for some real.
New York City... pizza?
We heard.
Heard what?
About you leaving to be on Broadway.
Look, I haven't made up my mind about anything.
We get it.
And we're happy for you.
You've inspired us in so many ways, so...
This is just another.
I don't understand.
Who-who told you guys?
Goolsby.
You okay, Mr. Shue?
I'm not going.
I'm staying with you guys.
I had my moment on the stage and it was glorious.
But you and I...
Have some unfinished business to take care of.
Now get out your notebooks.
Time to get to work.
Come on, this is Nationals, people.
Yes, Puck.
I want in, I want in.
Oh, gee!
We made it.
We're one of the top 50 show choirs in the nation.
Tomorrow only ten will move on to Showcase,
We have so got this.
Okay, usually I'm pretty cautious
I think we got a really good shot at winning this thing.
All right, everybody put your hand in the middle.
One, two, three.
New Directions!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ ♪
Peace up.
A town down.
Yeah. What?
♪ Okay ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm in the club with my homies ♪
♪ Trying to get a lil' V-I, keep it down on the low-key ♪.
They're really good.
♪ 'Cause you know how it is ♪
♪ I saw shorty, she was checkin' up on me ♪
♪ From the game she was spittin' in my ear ♪
♪ You would think that she knew me ♪
♪ I decided to chill ♪
♪ Conversation got heavy ♪
♪ She had me feeling like she's ready to blow ♪
♪ Watch out down below ♪
♪ Watch out, oh ♪
♪ Down below, watch out ♪
♪ She was saying "Come get me" ♪
♪ So I got up and followed her to the floor ♪
♪ She said "Baby, let's go" ♪
♪ Baby, let's go ♪
♪ When I told her, I said... ♪.
Hey. I gotta talk to you.
Hold on a sec.
I do this thing where I get my kids to sign
Yeah, well, don't bother getting us one.
I have a sneaking suspicion that we're about to kick your ass.
You're about to go up against the top show choirs
You're a bag of meat.
Take a large.
You're about a large, right?
Extra large.
What are you doing?
Buying you a T-shirt, Goolsby.
I'll send it to you...
After we win Nationals.
♪ Got the beat, got the beat, we got the beat. ♪.
Santana?
Oh, shoving your fingers down your throat
Vocal Adrenaline brothers and sisters?
I'm not throwing up on purpose.
I'm so nervous I can't keep any food down.
I used to love singing.
It was the only thing that relaxed me.
Now I hate it.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
No.
I think you're kind of mean, but I don't think you're stupid.
I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to get me to feel bad for you
What did I ever do to you to make you hate me so much?
When I came to your school,
I heard that the Glee Club
A safe place.
For some reason, you made me the only one who wasn't safe there.
Where are you going?
To the Philippine embassy.
I'm going to beg them to revoke my visa and deport me back home.
That's the only way
I'm going to be able to escape Vocal Adrenaline.
Wait... wait.
It's because you're good.
That's why I hated you.
That's why I sent you to that crack house.
I'm sorry.
But you have to go out there and sing.
You have a gift.
Something that Dustin
Goolsby would kill for.
I can't. I'm going to barf all over the stage.
If you feel like you're going to throw up, just look at me, and I'll help you through it.
Why?
Don't you want to win?
Guys like us have to stick together.
I'm going to hug you now.
And now, our returning champions from Carmel High,
Vocal Adrenaline.
What are you doing?
I'm making something right.
♪ Mmm... ♪
♪ Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm ♪
♪ All my life ♪
♪ I've waited for the right ♪
♪ Moment to let you know ♪
♪ I don't wanna let you go ♪
♪ But now I realize ♪
♪ There's just no perfect time ♪
♪ To confess how I feel ♪
♪ This much I know is real ♪
♪ So I refuse to ♪
♪ Waste one more second ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ Knowing ♪
♪ My... ♪
♪ Heart... ♪
♪ I don't need anything else ♪
♪ But your love ♪
♪ Nothing but you means ♪
♪ A thing to me ♪
♪ I'm incomplete ♪
♪ When you're not there ♪
♪ Holding me, touching me ♪
♪ I swear ♪
♪ All of the rest could just ♪
♪ Disappear ♪
♪ And I wouldn't even care ♪
♪ As long as you're there... ♪
♪ ♪
You wrote an amazing song, Finn.
I didn't know you had it in you.
Who cares about the song?
What I don't understand is, all you've ever wanted is
I-I am interested.
More than interested.
This is my dream.
Being here in New York.
I'm not gonna let anyone or anything keep me from it.
I'm sorry, Finn.
I love you.
But...
...there's nothing you can say or do
And now, from William McKinley
High in Lima, Ohio,
♪ Face to face ♪
♪ And heart to heart ♪
♪ We're so close ♪
♪ Yet so far apart ♪
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ I look away ♪
♪ That's just because ♪
♪ I'm not okay ♪
♪ But I hold on ♪
♪ I stay strong ♪
♪ Wondering if ♪
♪ We still belong... ♪
♪ Will we ever ♪
♪ Say the words ♪
♪ We're feeling ♪
♪ Reach down underneath and... ♪
I couldn't stay away.
♪ Will we ever ♪ From the show... or her?
♪ Have a happy ending ♪
♪ Or will we forever ♪
♪ Only be pretending? ♪
♪ Keeping secrets safe ♪
♪ Every move we make ♪
♪ Seems like no one's ♪
♪ Letting go ♪
♪ And it's ♪
♪ Such a shame 'cause if you ♪
♪ Feel the same ♪
♪ How am I ♪
♪ Supposed ♪
♪ To know... ♪
♪ Will we ever ♪
♪ Say the words we're feeling ♪
♪ Reach down underneath and ♪
♪ Tear down all the walls? ♪
♪ Will we ever ♪
♪ Have a happy ending ♪
♪ Or will we forever ♪
♪ Only be pretending? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ Pretending ♪
♪ Pretending... ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh... ♪
♪ Pretending... ♪.
Was that scripted?
No.
♪ ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ You and me keep on dancing ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ It's been tearing me apart ♪
♪ Never knowing what we are ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, you ♪
♪ And me keep on trying to play it cool ♪
♪ Now it's time to make a move ♪
♪ And that's what I'm gonna do ♪
♪ Lay it all down ♪
♪ Got something to say ♪
♪ Throw your doubt away ♪
♪ Do or die now ♪
♪ Step onto the plate ♪
♪ Blow the door wide open ♪
♪ Like up, up and away ♪
♪ Let's light up the world toni-I-ight ♪
♪ You got to give up the bark ♪
♪ And bi-I-ite ♪
♪ I know that we got the love all ri-I-ight ♪
♪ Come on and li-li-light it up ♪
♪ Light it up tonight ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, you ♪
♪ And me, turn it up ten thousand watts ♪
♪ Tell me why we've got to stop ♪
♪ I just want to let it rock, hey, hey, hey, you ♪
♪ And me keep on staring at the road ♪
♪ We don't know where to go, step back, let me take control ♪
♪ Lay it all down ♪
♪ Got something to say ♪
♪ Throw your doubt away ♪
♪ Do or die now ♪
♪ Step onto the plate ♪
♪ Blow the door wide open like ♪
♪ Up, up and away ♪
♪ Let's light up the world toni-I-ight ♪
♪ You got to give up the bark and bi-I-ite ♪
♪ I know that we got the love all ri-I-ight ♪
♪ Come on and li-li-light it up ♪
♪ Light it up tonight ♪
♪ Let's light up the world toni-I-ight ♪
♪ You got to give up the bark and bi-I-ite ♪
♪ I know that we got the love all ri-I-ight ♪
♪ Come on and li-li-light it up ♪
♪ Light it up tonight. ♪.
Don't you think this is gonna look so hot on Lord Tubbington?
I'm gonna go find it in an extra large.
I think we were good.
Good? We were amazing.
The kiss was... interesting.
Yeah, I'm-I'm calling it
The Kiss of the Century.
You're wrong, Finn.
That kiss was unprofessional.
It was too personal and intense.
The judges won't like it.
They'll consider it common
Nationals. Hi, Rachel.
You look amazing, and you sounded great.
Just shouldn't have kissed him.
Why are you here, Jessie?
For you.
Dude, back off.
You're just jealous.
Jealous of what we have,
It was the Superman of kisses.
It-It came with its own cape, right, Rachel?
What's-What's happening?
They just posted the top ten for showcase.
Everybody, gather around!
It's a moment
Okay, what should we do?
Let's go look at it... together.
Come on, come on.
Oh, I'm too nervous to look.
I'll go.
What did we place?
Well, Mr. Shue?
Say it. What did we rank?
We didn't.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
We aren't in the top ten.
Oh My God!
You should have seen it.
We all looked at the top ten list for Showcase,
And then Jessie kept going on and on
While I understand passion, I do think
Okay, then we get back to the hotel, and Santana loses it.
I mean, and the plane ride was completely silent.
Like, no one said a word.
We all just sat there with our faces buried
Wait, I don't get it.
You don't seem that sad at all.
Well, it was still amazing.
I mean, I flew on a plane for the first time in my life,
I had breakfast at Tiffany's,
I sang on a Broadway stage.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You know, when you stop and think about it,
Kurt Hummel's had a pretty good year.
Oh, look who's here.
Hey, what are you guys doing here?
Uh, nothing.
Just, uh, getting a coffee.
We ran into each other in the parking lot.
We're on our way to get some sheet music.
Tomorrow's my audition for the summer show at Six Flags.
Whereas I'm spending my summer composing Pip, Pip, Hooray!
The Broadway music about Pippa Middleton.
I have no idea who that is, but it sounds totally awesome.
We'll see you in class.
Bye.
Bye, guys.
Okay, so here are the nominees for my songs tomorrow.
I think I could probably...
Do you think they know?
I don't think anybody knows.
Hey.
You still pissed?
Do you think this voodoo doll looks enough
Come on. We can't be mad at Rachel forever.
Uh, yes, we can.
How could you possibly be so calm?
I don't know. I hated losing just as much as everyone,
Clearly, 'cause we got our asses kicked.
Yeah.
Sorry.
What was it about?
Acceptance.
I know that all the kids in the glee club... they fight,
Yeah, well, this is a club.
This is not a family.
Okay, well, family is a place
I know I'm going to be a bridesmaid at Mike
When they find an operation to make Artie's legs work again,
I'm going to be there for his first steps.
I love them.
I love everyone in Glee Club.
And I get to spend another year
What about you and I?
I love you, Santana.
I love you more
All I know about you and I is that, because of that,
I think anything's possible.
You're my best friend.
Yeah, me, too.
When did you get so smart?
Where have you been?
Hiding out.
Everyone hates me.
No, they don't.
It doesn't explain why
'Cause you should be more pissed at me than anyone else.
I screwed up!
I'm humiliated.
We worked so hard
Cost us the championship.
Look, being an artist
What were you feeling in that moment?
That I loved you.
And that I would have done or given anything
So you did.
You know, you gave it all up for one kiss.
Yeah.
Was it worth it?
What about you?
Was it worth it for you?
Yeah.
'Cause I know in my heart
You have to know that I...
I'm leaving, Finn.
I'm going to New York, and I'm never coming back.
Graduation's a year away.
You got any plans till then?
Okay. Let's go.
Where are we going?
Final Glee Club meeting of the year.
No other show choir
Hi.
Hiya. Come on.
You guys want to see what 12th place looks like?
Vietnamese subtitle credits to Itfriend. ORG Team
No mater which fansub translating it to Vietnamese!!
Sync by Thanh Hoang www.Itfriend.ORG www.MY-SUBS.com